// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following correctly describes C++ language",
    answer: "Type-less language",
    options: [
      "Statically typed language",
      "Dynamically typed language",
      "Both Statically and Dynamically typed language",
      "Type-less language"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is most preferred way of throwing exceptions?",
    answer: "Throw by refrence and catch by reference",
    options: [
      "Throw by value and catch by reference",
      "Throw by refrence and catch by reference",
      "Throw ny value and catch by value",
      "Throw the pointer value and provide catch for pointer type"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What does STL stands for?",
    answer: "Standard Template Library",
    options: [
      "Simple Template Library",
      "Standard Template Library",
      "Static Type Library",
      "Single-Type based Library"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "More than one user-defined functions can have the same name and perform different operations. This is a powerful feature of C++ and is known as ____?",
    answer: "function overloading",
    options: [
      "inheritance",
      "operator loading",
      "function overloading",
      "both c and b"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The header file ___ is a header file containing the declarations of cin and cout classes?",
    answer: "iostream.h",
    options: [
      "system.h",
      "Stdio.h",
      "iostream.h",
      " process.h"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The ___ and ___statements which we were using for input from keyboard and output to display screen C++.?",
    answer: " Cin, cout",
    options: [
      " Cin, cout",
      " scanf, printf",
      " system.out.println, printwriter",
      " cin, scanf"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The current reading position, which is the index of the next byte that will be read from the file is called ____. ",
    answer: " get pointer ",
    options: [
      " get pointer ",
      " set pointer",
      " curr pointer ",
      " put pointer "
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Data in the program was created by ___ and if more than one functions had to access data, ___ were used",
    answer: " Variables, global variables ",
    options: [
      "  variables, local variable ",
      " Variables, global variables ",
      " program name, automatic variable ",
      " variable, register variable "
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "State true or false <br> i) Attributes that are static only exist once for all instances of the class. <br>ii) If an attribute is declared final, its value can be changed. ",
    answer: " True, False ",
    options: [
      " True, False ",
      " False, False ",
      " True, True ",
      " False, True "
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "____ is the ability of objects belonging to different types to respond to method calls of methods of the same name, each one according to appropriate type-specific behaviour. ",
    answer: " Polymorphism ",
    options: [
      " Inheritance ",
      " Virtuality ",
      " Polymorphism ",
      " None of these "
    ]
  },
];